trailfire.com 2012-07-05

# Trailfire Privacy Policy

Trailfire.com is a service of Trailfire, Inc. ("Trailfire" or "we"). Trailfire respects your individual privacy and is opposed to spyware. This privacy policy documents our standards for the protection of your personal information. The policy is effective as of October 27, 2006, applies to information collected through the site Trailfire.com, and covers the following areas: what personally identifiable information is collected by Trailfire or by any third party through our site; how Trailfire uses this information; with whom Trailfire may share this information; what choices are available to you as a user of the site with respect to collection, use and distribution of the information; what types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## 1\. Information Collection and Use

Trailfire collects information on the site at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the site. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of our site. Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information for you to use certain features of the site. For example, when you register as a member of Trailfire, you must submit an e-mail address and choose a username. Generally, Trailfire does not collect personally identifiable information other than username and e-mail address from its registered users. 

## 2\. Personal Information of Children Under 13

Trailfire complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and the FTC's Rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR 512). This site is not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age through this site. If you are under age 13, you are not eligible to become a registered user of Trailfire. 

## 3\. Use of Your Personal Information

If you become a registered user of Trailfire and install Trailfire's plug-in software for your browser, the Trailfire software will create a record of web pages you mark (place your own flags or comments) using the software and the content posted by you for that page. These records are a necessary and integral part of the service, and are used in the same way that a blog service stores comments and links for retrieval by others. We do not keep records or use any information about the various websites you visit or other content you view that are not marked by you for retrieval through Trailfire. We only store the sites and contents you mark as part of our service. Moreover, unless we determine that you may have violated the Trailfire Terms of Service, we will not attempt to learn your real name, address, telephone number or other similar kinds of information other than your e-mail address. If we or a trusted third party use your e-mail address to contact you regarding additional products or services, you will always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving that kind of communication in the future in conformance with the CAN-SPAM Act (15 USC 7701 et seq). 

## 4\. Use of Aggregate Information

We may store non-personally identifiable information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our user community in the aggregate. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks which we will use to analyze trends, administer the site, track aggregate service and web site usage patterns, and gather broad demographic information for general use. Trailfire is not spyware. Unlike spyware, usage information recorded in our log files is not linked to personally identifiable information. Although we may share our aggregate information with third parties or the public, our use and disclosure of this aggregate information will never intrude on your individual privacy rights. Your individual usage cannot be tracked through aggregate data. 

## 5\. Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others. 

## 6\. Business Transitions

In the event Trailfire goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, our customers' personal information may be part of the assets transferred. Customers will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. 

## 7\. Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Trailfire is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our site. 

## 8\. Security

Trailfire takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. 

## 9\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information. 

## 10\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our stated privacy policy, we will prominently post a notice on the main page and other pages of the Trailfire site to alert you to the update. If we decide to make a change to the way we use your existing personally identifiable information that is materially different from the policy stated at the time of its collection, we will take two steps: (1) we will state in our posted update notice that personally identifiable information is affected, and (2) we will either exclude your personally identifiable information from that new use or before we use your information notify you via e-mail and give you a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. 

## 11\. Contact Information

Trailfire, Inc.  
101 Yesler Way, Suite 207  
Seattle, WA 98104  
FAX (206) 254-0596
